https://andersongardens.org/about/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Your Privacy We are committed to the protection of your privacy on this website. This site does not collect personal information such as names and email addresses unless individuals knowingly provide that information.   Policy on Information Collection The website collects personal information for membership purchases and renewals, program registrations, electronic newsletters and mailings, and general inquiries. This information is used only for the intended services. For some of these services, the site may request information about background, occupation, demographics, and interests.   The website automatically collects information about computer hardware and software. This can include IP addresses, browser types, domain names, access times, and the referring websites that visitors use to access this website. The site uses this information to maintain the quality of the service while you are on the website, as well as to collect general statistics about the site.   Policy on Information Disclosure This site collects personal information to operate the site and to deliver the services you request. This information helps us understand our audience, and that allows us to better meet the needs of website users. We will not sell, trade, or rent personal information. We may compile aggregate statistics and provide them to third parties, but these statistics will not include information that identifies individual website users.   We may save personal information to comply with federal and state policies, but we will not disclose this information to third parties or government agencies unless we are required to do so by state or federal law or we must act under exigent circumstances to protect the safety of our users or the public.   Revisions to the Privacy Policy The privacy policy may be revised at any time. We may revise the policy in response to changes in the law or other factors. We encourage website users to periodically visit this page to review the most current policy.
